Welcome to the
Manualif Vietnam app.  To submit an
insurance claim or
compensation request, please log
in quickly on the Manul Vietnam app
using facial recognition or
fingerprint authentication.  On the main screen, you can either
click the "Create Claim" button
for a service or click the "Claims" tab
at the bottom of the screen and select a
claim.  Please view the
step-by-step instructions for creating a claim
by swiping the screen from right
to left.  After reviewing the instructions, please
click Start to initiate your
request.  On this screen, you
select the insured person for whom you
wish to file the claim.  Press continue.  Please
select the insurance event corresponding to the
claim for the selected insured person
from the list of insurance benefits
displayed on the screen.  You
can click on the instructions to refer to the
definition of insurance benefits in order to choose the most
suitable benefit.
Next, please provide the
required information related to the insured event
and click continue.
At this step, please upload the
pre-prepared supporting documents
in PDF or image format.  You
can view a list of required documents
or download sample documents for reference
and to supplement your claim file.
Please ensure that all required documents have
been uploaded.  Then press
continue.  Please select your preferred method of receiving
compensation, choose to update your
bank account, and follow the instructions if you do not already
have your compensation account information
.  Finally, please
carefully review the information you have provided,
update or correct it if
necessary, and click submit request.  After
confirming your agreement to the terms and
conditions, your claim
has been processed.  Manuliz will review your application and
notify you of the results as soon as possible
.  You can track the
processing status of your claim in a claims history section
on the Manulif Vietnam app.
With Manulif Vietnam, managing
insurance policies and using online services
has never been easier.  The
Manolif Vietnam app is available on the App
Store and the CHPL store.  You're ready
to experience it.  Download the Manulife
Vietnam app today to enjoy a
better life every day.